[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 7 and height 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "3.5",
      "options": [
        "3.5",
        "1.0",
        "7.5",
        "6.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 15 and height 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "22.5",
      "options": [
        "22.5",
        "26.5",
        "20.0",
        "25.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 6 and height 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "42.0",
      "options": [
        "42.0",
        "44.5",
        "39.5",
        "46.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 16 and height 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "104.0",
      "options": [
        "104.0",
        "106.5",
        "108.0",
        "101.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 4 and height 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "28.0",
      "options": [
        "28.0",
        "30.5",
        "32.0",
        "25.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 13 and height 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "104.0",
      "options": [
        "106.5",
        "101.5",
        "108.0",
        "104.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 13 and height 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "26.0",
      "options": [
        "28.5",
        "30.0",
        "23.5",
        "26.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 13 and height 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "65.0",
      "options": [
        "65.0",
        "62.5",
        "69.0",
        "67.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "60.5",
      "options": [
        "64.5",
        "60.5",
        "58.0",
        "63.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 18 and height 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "144.0",
      "options": [
        "141.5",
        "146.5",
        "148.0",
        "144.0"
      ]
    }
]